Reap what you sow.
The Price We Pay is a action, thriller, mystery
film directed by Ryuhei Kitamura.
After a pawn shop robbery goes askew, two criminals take refuge at a remote farmhouse
to try to let the heat die down, but find something much more menacing.
Adam, played by Emile Hirsch.
Cody, played by Stephen Dorff.
Grace, played by Gigi Zumbado.
Danny, played by Tyler Sanders.
Jodi, played by Erika Ervin.
John, played by Jesse Kinser.
The Price We Pay is a 2022 American horror film directed by Ryuhei
Kitamura and starring Emile Hirsch and Stephen Dorff.
The film was released on video on demand on January 10, 2023,
and in select theaters on January 13, 2023.
The film explores themes of farm, robbery, war veteran, hostage, robber.
The tone is mind_bending and dark and intense.